Office of the Board of Trustees Records UA003
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Board of Visitors Committee, 1900 -- 1978; UA003.012; 1.7 Linear Feet
  - Benefactors: Stearns Estate, 1920 -- 1926; UA003.012.034.00005 (Box 34)
  - Benefactors: Sweet Estate, UA003.012.034.00006 (Box 34)
  - Benefactors: John Wade Estate, UA003.012.034.00007 (Box 34)
  - Benefactors: William P. West Fund, UA003.012.034.00008 (Box 34)
  - Benefactors: Whitney Estate, UA003.012.034.00009 (Box 34)
  - Benefactors: Alma G. Wiley Estate, UA003.012.034.00010 (Box 34)
  - Board of Visitors:General, 1934 -- 1978; UA003.012.034.00011 (Box 34)
  - Board of Visitors:BSOT (1), 1960 -- 1962; UA003.012.034.00012 (Box 34)
  - Board of Visitors:BSOT (2), 1963 -- 1965; UA003.012.034.00013 (Box 34)
  - Board of Visitors: Chemistry, UA003.012.034.00014 (Box 34)
  - Board of Visitors, 1900 -- 1905; UA003.012.090.00001 (Box 90)
  - Board of Visitors, 1905 -- 1931; UA003.012.090.00002 (Box 90)
  - Board of Visitors, June 9, UA003.012.090.00003 (Box 90)
- Investment Committee, 1993 -- 2020; UA003.013; 1.95 Linear Feet; 19 Digital Object(s) 19 zip files containing 424 files.; .54 Gigabytes
  This series contains materials from Tufts University's Investment Committee from 1993 to 1998. Items include agendas, minutes, memoranda, letters, and reports.
  The Investment Committee, a sub-committee of the Administration and Finance Committee, is responsible for the financial investments of the university.
  - Investment, November 5, 1993; UA003.013.061.00001 (Box 61)
  - Investment, February 25, 1994; UA003.013.061.00002 (Box 61)
  - Investment, May 20, 1994; UA003.013.061.00003 (Box 61)
  - Investment, February 10, 1995; UA003.013.062.00001 (Box 62)
  - Investment, May 19, 1995; UA003.013.062.00002 (Box 62)
  - Investment, May 19, 1995; UA003.013.063.00001 (Box 63)
  - Investment, August 22, 1995; UA003.013.063.00002 (Box 63)
  - Investment, November 13, 1995; UA003.013.063.00003 (Box 63)
  - Investment Committee, February 9, 1996; UA003.013.093.00001 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee, April 25, 1996; UA003.013.093.00002 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee, February 7, 1997; UA003.013.093.00003 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee, May 16, 1997; UA003.013.093.00004 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee, October 16, 1997; UA003.013.093.00005 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee, November 24, 1997; UA003.013.093.00006 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee, April 16, 1998; UA003.013.093.00007 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee, July 8, 1998; UA003.013.093.00008 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee, August 7, 1998; UA003.013.093.00009 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee, September 29, 1998; UA003.013.093.00010 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee, March 15, 1999; UA003.013.093.00011 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee, November 6, 1999; UA003.013.093.00012 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee, March 7, 2000; UA003.013.093.00013 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee, November 28, 2000; UA003.013.093.00014 (Box 93)
  - Investment Committee working papers, 2007 -- 2009; UA003.013.130; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 130, Folder 1 - 12)
  - Investment committee files, 2005-2016; UA003.013.00001; 323 Digital Object(s); 0.35 Gigabytes
  - Investment committee files, 2016; UA003.013.00002; 10 Digital Object(s); .01 Gigabytes
  - Investment committee files, 2017; UA003.013.00003; 5 Digital Object(s); 5.43 Megabytes
  - Investment committee files, 2017; UA003.013.00004; 6 Digital Object(s); 8.11 Megabytes
  - Investment committee files, 2017; UA003.013.00005; 5 Digital Object(s); 8.9 Megabytes
  - Investment committee files, 2017; UA003.013.00006; 5 Digital Object(s); 8.07 Megabytes
  - Investment committee files, 2018; UA003.013.00007; 6 Digital Object(s); 10.4 Megabytes
  - Investment committee files, 2018; UA003.013.00008; 7 Digital Object(s); 12.4 Megabytes
  - Investment Committee files, 2018-07-26; UA003.013.00009; 4 Digital Object(s); 8.27 Megabytes
  - Investment Committee files, 2018-10-25; UA003.013.00010; 5 Digital Object(s); 13.19 Megabytes
  - Investment Committee files, 2019-01-24; UA003.013.00011; 5 Digital Object(s); 11.5 Megabytes
  - Investment Committee files, 2019-04-25; UA003.013.00012; 5 Digital Object(s); 8.05 Megabytes
  - Investment Committee files, 2019 July 25; UA003.002336; 6 Megabytes 4 files
  - Investment Committee files, 2019 October 24; UA003.002337; 8.8 Megabytes 6 files
  - Investment Committee files, 2020 February 23; UA003.002396; 8.62 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
  - Investment Committee files, 2020 March 23; UA003.002397; 3.2 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
  - Investment Committee files, 2020 April 23; UA003.002398; 11.98 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
  - Investment Committee files, 2020 July 23; UA003.002399; 12.65 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 5 files.
  - Investment Committee files, 2020 October 22; UA003.002400; 13.08 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 6 files.
- Compiled Subject Files, 1848 -- 1999; 1867 -- 1983; UA003.014; 4.75 Linear Feet
  - Deed: Bentley Block, 1892 -- 1906; UA003.002303; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30)
  - Deed: Barnard Estate, 1856 -- 1905; UA003.002304; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30)
  - Deed: Howe Estate, 1897 -- 1899; UA003.002305; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30)
  - Title insurance policy for Tufts College, 1899 -- 1899; UA003.002306; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30)
  - Deeds and Correspondence: Dearborn Estate, Tacoma, WA, 1888 -- 1903; UA003.002307; 2 Folder(s) (Box 30)
  - Deeds and Correspondence: Dearborn Estate, Seattle, WA, 1888 -- 1903; UA003.002308; 2 Folder(s) (Box 30)
  - Loose Correspondence: Dearborn Estates, miscellaneous, 1894 -- 1903; UA003.002309; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30)
  - Deeds and Correspondence: Dearborn Estate, Lyndon, KS, 1891 -- 1902; UA003.002310; 2 Folder(s) (Box 30)
  - Checks and notes to the $30,000 Fund, 1859 -- 1884; UA003.002311; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30)
  - Benefactors: Eleanor Atherton Estate, UA003.014.032.00001 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Lester Avnet Trust, UA003.014.032.00002 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Bacon Estate, UA003.014.032.00003 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: James Bigelow Estate, UA003.014.032.00004 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Robert Billings, UA003.014.032.00005 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Betsy Blake Estate, UA003.014.032.00006 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Charlton Fund, UA003.014.032.00007 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Mary Churchill Trust, UA003.014.032.00008 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Charles Clark Estate, UA003.014.032.00009 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Mary B. Cousins Estate, UA003.014.032.00010 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: William Dameshek Estate, UA003.014.032.00011 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Mabel Daniels Estate, UA003.014.032.00012 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Amelia Dyer Estate, UA003.014.032.00013 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Fletcher Estate, UA003.014.032.00014 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Volney Sewell Fulham Fund, UA003.014.032.00015 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Ginn Estate, UA003.014.032.00016 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: W. Chester Haley, UA003.014.032.00017 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Hodgdon Estate, UA003.014.032.00018 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Agnes F. Judkins Estate, UA003.014.032.00019 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Toivo Laminan Estate, UA003.014.032.00020 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Berndt S. Mansfeldt Estate, UA003.014.032.00021 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Grace Mansfield Estate, UA003.014.032.00022 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: A.A. Miner, UA003.014.032.00023 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Packard Fund, UA003.014.032.00024 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: Charles Page Estate, UA003.014.032.00025 (Box 32)
  - Benefactors: George Risergari Trust, UA003.014.032.00026 (Box 32)
  - Board of Visitors: (1) Crane Theological School, 1883 -- 1939; UA003.014.035.00001 (Box 35)
  - Board of Visitors: Dental School, 1903 -- 1941; UA003.014.035.00002 (Box 35)
  - Board of Visitors: Eliot-Pearson Dept. of Child Study, 1964, UA003.014.035.00003 (Box 35)
  - Board of Visitors: Engineering, 1906 -- 1935; UA003.014.035.00004 (Box 35)
  - Board of Visitors: Jackson, 1911 -- 1939; UA003.014.035.00005 (Box 35)
  - Board of Visitors: Liberal Arts, 1885 -- 1935; UA003.014.035.00006 (Box 35)
  - Board of Visitors: Libraries, 1968, UA003.014.035.00007 (Box 35)
  - Board of Visitors: Medical School, 1905 -- 1927; UA003.014.035.00008 (Box 35)
  - Boarding house contract between Josiah W. Talbot and Tufts College, July 23, 1855; UA003.002302; 0.1 Linear Feet (Box 44)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Committee on, 1903 -- 1981; UA003.014.035.00009 (Box 35)
  - Bylaws, 1881 -- 1999; UA003.014.035.00010 (Box 35)
  - Correspondence and Individual Amendments to By-Laws, UA003.014.035.00011 (Box 35)
  - Charter, 1886 -- 1962; UA003.014.035.00012 (Box 35)
  - Correspondence (1955-65), 1955 -- 1965; UA003.014.036.00001 (Box 36)
  - Development Committee: General, 1975 -- 1980; UA003.014.036.00002 (Box 36)
  - Development Committee: Handbook Meetings (1977-79), 1977 -- 1979; UA003.014.036.00003 (Box 36)
  - Development Committee: Reports, Meetings,1980 (1), UA003.014.036.00004 (Box 36)
  - Development Committee: Reports, Meetings,1980 (2), UA003.014.036.00005 (Box 36)
  - Development Committee: Campaign for Tufts, UA003.014.036.00006 (Box 36)
  - Executive Committee (1856-1941), UA003.014.037.00001 (Box 37)
  - Finance Committee (Insurance), UA003.014.037.00002 (Box 37)
  - Finance Committee: General (1), UA003.014.037.00003 (Box 37)
  - Finance Committee, UA003.014.037.00004 (Box 37)
  - Finance Committee: General (2), UA003.014.037.00005 (Box 37)
  - Treasurer/Finance Committee, 1855 -- 1867; UA003.014.037.00006 (Box 37)
  - Finance Committee, 1867 -- 1869; UA003.014.038.00001 (Box 38)
  - Treasurer/Finance Committee (1870-72), 1870 -- 1872; UA003.014.038.00002 (Box 38)
  - Finance Committee, 1872 -- 1874; UA003.014.038.00003 (Box 38)
  - Treasurer/Finance Committee (1875-79), 1875 -- 1879; UA003.014.039.00001 (Box 39)
  - Treasurer/Term Bills, UA003.014.039.00002 (Box 39)
  - Finances: Fund Raising (pre 1860), UA003.014.039.00003 (Box 39)
  - Finances: Fund Raising (1861-1910), UA003.014.039.00004 (Box 39)
  - Treasurer/Finances Committee (1880), UA003.014.039.00005 (Box 39)
  - Treasurer's Committee/Finance 1880-1946, UA003.014.039.00006 (Box 39)
  - Finances: Fund Raising (Financial Agent), UA003.014.039.00007 (Box 39)
  - Treasurer's Report, UA003.014.040.00001 (Box 40)
  - Treasurer's Report, UA003.014.040.00002 (Box 40)
  - Treasurer's Report, UA003.014.040.00003 (Box 40)
  - Mortgage Deeds, UA003.014.041.00001 (Box 41)
  - Mortgage Deeds, UA003.014.041.00002 (Box 41)
  - Mortgage Deeds, UA003.014.041.00003 (Box 41)
  - Mortgage Deeds, UA003.014.041.00004 (Box 41)
  - Mortgage Deeds, UA003.014.041.00005 (Box 41)
  - Subscriptions, 1848 -- 1851; UA003.014.042.00001 (Box 42)
  - Finances: Investment, Investment Property (1), UA003.014.042.00002 (Box 42)
  - Finances: Investment, Investment Property (2), UA003.014.042.00003 (Box 42)
  - Finances: Foundations, Research Grants (General), UA003.014.042.00004 (Box 42)
  - Finances: Foundation & Research Grants: W.K. Kellogg Foundation (1942-56), 1942 -- 1956; UA003.014.043.00001 (Box 43)
  - Finances: Foundation & Research Grants: Kresge Foundation (1950-51), 1950 -- 1951; UA003.014.043.00002 (Box 43)
  - Finances: Foundation & Research Grants: Link Foundation (1954-61), 1954 -- 1961; UA003.014.043.00003 (Box 43)
  - Finances: Foundation & Research Grants: Rockefeller Foundation (1939-56), 1939 -- 1956; UA003.014.043.00004 (Box 43)
  - Finances: Indenture of Mortgages; Deed of Trust 1968, UA003.014.043.00005 (Box 43)
  - Finances: Treasurers Reports (1923-35), 1923 -- 1935; UA003.014.043.00006 (Box 43)
  - Trustee: General Education Board (1906-07), 1906 -- 1907; UA003.014.043.00007 (Box 43)
  - 1889-(1905-37)-1968, 1889 -- 1968; UA003.014.043.00008 (Box 43)
  - Honorary Degrees: Policies, UA003.014.043.00009 (Box 43)
  - Real Estate (mold) 1889-(1905-37)-1968, 1889 -- 1968; UA003.014.044.00001 (Box 44)
  - Mortgage Deeds, UA003.014.044.00002 (Box 44)
  - Trustees: Finances -- Foundation and Research Grants, Braitmayer Foundation, 1965 -- 1969; UA003.014.044.00003 (Box 44)
  - Finances: Foundation and Research Grants, Carnegie Corp. of New York (1925-54), 1925 -- 1954; UA003.014.044.00004 (Box 44)
  - Finances: Foundation and Research Grants, Hayden Foundation (1955-57), 1955 -- 1957; UA003.014.044.00005 (Box 44)
  - Deeds: Mason Estate, 1905; UA003.002312; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30)
  - Lease and Correspondence: Jackson Estate, 1880 -- 1900; UA003.002313; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30)
  - Deeds: Gray Estate, 1899 -- 1903; UA003.002314; 2 Folder(s) (Box 30)
  - Deeds and Correspondence: Minnesota Estate, 1884 -- 1903; UA003.002315; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30)
  - Deeds and Correspondence: Kioua Country Estate, 1892 -- 1902; UA003.002316; 1 Folder(s) (Box 30)
- Artifacts and photographs, 1900 -- 1963; UA003.015; 0.25 Linear Feet; 1 Artifact(s)
  This series contains a bust of Newton Talbot and a few photographs.
  This series is not arranged.
  - Newton Talbot Bust, 1900; UA003.015.001.00001 (Box Shared 10)
    The date is approximate. The bust is in the Level G DCA office. On loan from Art Gallery (AI 49800) - see collection documentation folder for Art Gallery for loan form.
  - Trustees Dinner photographs, 1951 -- 1963; UA003.015.001.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    Moved from former PC collection.
- Office files, 1939 -- 2020; 1970 -- 2000; UA003.016; 3.6 Linear Feet; 6 Digital Object(s) 6 digital objects comprising 18 files.
  This series contains files created and maintained in the functioning of the Office of the Board of Trustees. This is maintained as a separate series due to the questionable provenance of the other subject file series.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by accession.
  - ABS Conference Tufts July 2000 Board Secretaries, UA003.016.116.00001 (Box 116)
  - Academic Freedom, tenure, retire [policies and working papers], 2000; UA003.016.116.00002 (Box 116)
    Contains folders Arts and Sciences Tenure and Promotion and Working Papers, Old Policy; See also information from one floppy disk.
    - Academic Freedom, tenure, retire [policies and working papers], 2000; UA003.016.116.00002.00001
  - Acceditation, 1997; UA003.016.116.00003 (Box 116)
  - Accounting-authorization, 1997; UA003.016.116.00004 (Box 116)
  - Admissions data policies and proceed, 1975 -- 2005; UA003.016.116.00005 (Box 116)
    Contains folders "Admissions data," "agreements, Chinese Benevolent Society" and "Affirmative Action"
  - Agenda Topics, 1996; UA003.016.116.00006 (Box 116)
  - Alcohol, 1982 -- 1985; UA003.016.116.00007 (Box 116)
  - Annual reports, 1999 -- 2000; UA003.016.116.00008 (Box 116)
  - Appointments and resignations (officers), 2005; UA003.016.116.00009 (Box 116)
  - Archives, 1982 -- 1998; UA003.016.116.00010 (Box 116)
    History of Archives pre and post DCA
  - Attorney General, 1996; UA003.016.116.00011 (Box 116)
  - Bequsts/wills, 1995 -- 2007; UA003.016.116.00012 (Box 116)
  - Biomedical research and nutrition complex 10/94, 1991 -- 1994; UA003.016.116.00013 (Box 116)
  - Bonds-MHEFA, 1982 -- 1983; UA003.016.116.00014 (Box 116)
  - Bond closing info, 1978 -- 1984; UA003.016.116.00015 (Box 116)
  - Bond closing (cont'd), 1975 -- 1984; UA003.016.116.00016 (Box 116)
  - BSOT, 1958 -- 1982; UA003.016.116.00017 (Box 116)
  - Buildings, Arts Complex, 1981 -- 1989; UA003.016.116.00018 (Box 116)
  - Bush [Vannevar], 1980 -- 1999; UA003.016.116.00019 (Box 116)
  - Campus master plan, 1986 -- 1990; UA003.016.116.00020 (Box 116)
  - Capital campaign, 1987 -- 1991; UA003.016.116.00021 (Box 116)
  - Centers, 1984 -- 1998; UA003.016.116.00022 (Box 116)
    Includes folders on Career Planning and Center for Environmental Management.
  - Certifications, 1975 -- 2000; UA003.016.116.00023 (Box 116)
  - Combined degree programs, 1985; UA003.016.116.00024 (Box 116)
    MD/MBA
  - Contracts, 1995 -- 2001; UA003.016.116.00025 (Box 116)
  - Commencement 1992 and earlier, 1980 -- 1992; UA003.016.116.00026 (Box 116)
  - Commencement, 1993; UA003.016.116.00027 (Box 116)
  - Commencement, 1994; UA003.016.116.00028 (Box 116)
  - Commencement, 1995; UA003.016.116.00029 (Box 116)
  - Commencement '96, 1996; UA003.016.116.00030 (Box 116)
  - Commencement, 1997; UA003.016.117.00001 (Box 117)
  - Commencement, 1998; UA003.016.117.00002 (Box 117)
  - Commencement, 1999; UA003.016.117.00003 (Box 117)
  - Commencement, 2000; UA003.016.117.00004 (Box 117)
  - Commencement, 2001; UA003.016.117.00005 (Box 117)
  - Copy services, 2001; UA003.016.117.00006 (Box 117)
  - [Correspondence], 2002; UA003.016.117.00007 (Box 117)
    Sally Kiely retirement
  - Correspondence, 1997; UA003.016.117.00008 (Box 117)
  - Deeds, 1978 -- 1979; UA003.016.117.00009 (Box 117)
  - Degree program, 1994 -- 1998; UA003.016.117.00010 (Box 117)
  - Degrees - Types Awarded, 1976; UA003.016.117.00011 (Box 117)
    language used on diplomas
  - Development presentations, 1997; UA003.016.117.00012 (Box 117)
  - DiBiaggio [President], 1992 -- 2002; UA003.016.117.00013 (Box 117)
  - DiBiaggio Chair, 2001; UA003.016.117.00014 (Box 117)
  - DiBiaggio Inauguration, 1993; UA003.016.117.00015 (Box 117)
  - Dual Degree program, 1993 -- 1998; UA003.016.117.00016 (Box 117)
  - Divestment [1], 1978 -- 1991; UA003.016.117.00017 (Box 117)
  - Divestment [2], 1979 -- 1989; UA003.016.117.00018 (Box 117)
  - Endowed Chairs [1], 1981 -- 2001; UA003.016.117.00019 (Box 117)
  - Endowed Chairs [2], 1984 -- 1999; UA003.016.117.00020 (Box 117)
  - Endowed Chairs [3], 1981 -- 1995; UA003.016.117.00021 (Box 117)
  - Endowed professorships, 1971; UA003.016.117.00022 (Box 117)
  - Endowment book, 1999; UA003.016.117.00023 (Box 117)
  - Engineering-College-Misc., 1985; UA003.016.117.00024 (Box 117)
  - Fact Book update, 2000; UA003.016.117.00025 (Box 117)
  - Faculty, 1975 -- 2002; UA003.016.117.00026 (Box 117)
  - Faculty diversity, 2002; UA003.016.117.00027 (Box 117)
  - Faculty luncheon, 2000; UA003.016.117.00028 (Box 117)
  - Fares Lecture series, 1996 -- 1998; UA003.016.117.00029 (Box 117)
  - General mailbox email 'Trustees', 2001; UA003.016.117.00030 (Box 117)
  - Goddard Chapel, 2003; UA003.016.117.00031 (Box 117)
  - Grant, Gina, 1995; UA003.016.117.00032 (Box 117)
  - Grants, 1991 -- 1993; UA003.016.117.00033 (Box 117)
  - Gun Collection-Victor A. Friend, 1978 -- 1979; UA003.016.117.00034 (Box 117)
  - Herter Fund, 1995; UA003.016.117.00035 (Box 117)
  - Human Nutrition Research Center (HNRC), 1983 -- 1996; UA003.016.117.00036 (Box 117)
  - Hydro-Quebec, 1989 -- 1994; UA003.016.117.00037 (Box 117)
  - Institutes, 1976; UA003.016.117.00038 (Box 117)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1988 -- 1990; UA003.016.117.00039 (Box 117)
  - International Famine Center, 1995; UA003.016.117.00040 (Box 117)
  - Jaharis Family Center, 1994 -- 2005; UA003.016.118.00001 (Box 118)
  - Lambert, Joseph, 1996; UA003.016.118.00002 (Box 118)
  - Library - Health Sciences, 1999; UA003.016.118.00003 (Box 118)
  - Library - Tisch, 1996; UA003.016.118.00004 (Box 118)
  - Lincoln Filene Center, 1980 -- 1998; UA003.016.118.00005 (Box 118)
  - Long Term Planning, 1971 -- 1973; UA003.016.118.00006 (Box 118)
  - Medical School, 1993; UA003.016.118.00007 (Box 118)
  - Meyer [Jean], 1976 -- 1993; UA003.016.118.00008 (Box 118)
  - Mount Auburn Cemetary, 1979 -- 1985; UA003.016.118.00009 (Box 118)
  - Nutrition Institute (graduate A and S), 1981 -- 2001; UA003.016.118.00010 (Box 118)
  - Patent and copyright policies, 1963 -- 1980; UA003.016.118.00011 (Box 118)
  - Policy - Research, 1995 -- 1997; UA003.016.118.00012 (Box 118)
  - Policy - University, 1993 -- 2004; UA003.016.118.00013 (Box 118)
  - Records retention, 1990 -- 1995; UA003.016.118.00014 (Box 118)
  - ROTC - Elimination of, 1969 -- 1973; UA003.016.118.00015 (Box 118)
  - Sackler School, 1985 -- 1993; UA003.016.118.00016 (Box 118)
  - Schools, Crane Theological School, 1993; UA003.016.118.00017 (Box 118)
  - Special Studies, College of, 1939 -- 1986; UA003.016.118.00018 (Box 118)
  - State Regional Boards of Education, 1974 -- 1987; UA003.016.118.00019 (Box 118)
  - Strategic Plan November, 1999; UA003.016.118.00020 (Box 118)
    - Strategic Plan November 1999 [files], UA003.016.118.00020.00001; Unknown (Box 118)
    - Strategic Plan November 1999 [preservation files], UA003.016.118.00020.00002; Unknown
  - Student Activity Fee, 1977 -- 1981; UA003.016.118.00021 (Box 118)
  - Student organizations, 1996; UA003.016.118.00022 (Box 118)
  - Surveys (senior), 1993 -- 1996; UA003.016.118.00023 (Box 118)
  - T-NEMC, 1968 -- 2004; UA003.016.118.00024 (Box 118)
  - Task Force on Race, 1997; UA003.016.118.00025 (Box 118)
  - Tenure Other, 1966 -- 1982; UA003.016.118.00026 (Box 118)
  - Tenure Policy, 1976 -- 1987; UA003.016.118.00027 (Box 118)
  - Tenure Schools, 1970 -- 1996; UA003.016.118.00028 (Box 118)
  - TMCA Foundation, 1975; UA003.016.118.00029 (Box 118)
  - Trustee Dialog Series, 1994 -- 2003; UA003.016.118.00030 (Box 118)
  - Trustee Handbook, 1986 -- 1987; UA003.016.118.00031 (Box 118)
  - Trustees of Tufts University, 2002; UA003.016.118.00032 (Box 118)
  - Tufts Seal - Corporate, 1955 -- 2006; UA003.016.118.00033 (Box 118)
  - Tufts Managed Care Institute, 1995; UA003.016.118.00034 (Box 118)
  - TU Express, 1972; UA003.016.118.00035 (Box 118)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1973; UA003.016.118.00036 (Box 118)
  - U.S. News and World Report, 1992 -- 2000; UA003.016.118.00037 (Box 118)
  - Veterinary School [1 of 2], 1976; UA003.016.118.00038 (Box 118)
  - Veterinary School [2 of 2], 1975 -- 2004; UA003.016.118.00039 (Box 118)
  - Vision Statement, 1994; UA003.016.118.00040 (Box 118)
  - New Trustee Orientation files, 2019-02-07; UA003.016.00001; 5 Digital Object(s); 3.75 Megabytes
  - New trustee orientation files, 2020 February 06; UA003.002401; 54.85 Kilobytes; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1 file.
- Trustees Weekend Working Papers and Minutes, 1995 -- 2019; UA003.017; 2.4 Linear Feet; 45 Digital Object(s) Containing 7893 files; 7.92 Gigabytes
  This series contains files created and maintained in preparation and execution of Trustees Weekends held three times a year. These records include multiple committees. Documenations for specific committees may be duplicated in individual committee series.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Trustees Weekend 1995/1996 [Binder] Front Material [1 of 4], 1911 -- 1995; UA003.017.083.00001 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - Trustees Weekend 1995/1996 [Binder] [2 of 4], 1911 -- 1995; UA003.017.083.00002 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - Trustees Weekend 1995/1996 [Binder] [3 of 4], 1902 -- 1996; UA003.017.083.00003 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - Trustees Weekend 1995/1996 [Binder] [4 of 4], 1905 -- 1996; UA003.017.083.00004 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes], 1902 -- 1996; UA003.017.083.00005 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes], 1905 -- 1996; UA003.017.083.00006 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes], 1911 -- 1996; UA003.017.083.00007 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes], 1911 -- 1996; UA003.017.083.00008 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes], 1901 -- 1997; UA003.017.083.00009 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes], 1902 -- 1997; UA003.017.083.00010 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - Retreat Committee [Working papers and minutes], 1902 -- 1997; UA003.017.083.00011 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes], 1903 -- 1997; UA003.017.083.00012 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes], 1905 -- 1997; UA003.017.083.00013 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes], 1909 -- 1997; UA003.017.083.00014 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes] [1 of 2], 1911 -- 1997; UA003.017.083.00015 (Box UA003 Shared 5)
  - [Working papers and minutes] [2 of 2], 1911 -- 1997; UA003.017.083.00016 (Box UA003 Shared 5)